

## CHANDRA RAMDHAN PURNAMA

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

"I am not a visionary. I'm an engineer. I'm happy with the people who are wandering around looking at the stars but I am looking at the ground and I want to fix the pothole before I fall in" - Linus Torvalds

#### CONTACT

- (+62) 838-2189-6126
- euclife@outlook.co.id
- in chandraramdhan
- https:/euclife.github.io/
- 33 Manglid Street Bandung, Indonesia

# PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE -

PHP
JAVA
C++
C#
C
JAVA SCRIPT
GO

**PYTHON** 

### OTHER LANGUAGE

HTML

XML

CSS

SQL

INDONESIAN

ENGLISH

## PROGAMMING FRAMEWORK

LARAVEL
WORDPRESS
OCTOBER CMS
NODE JS
EXPRESS JS
DJANGO
ASP.NET

#### **OTHER SKILLS**

COREL DRAW

MS. OFFICE

JQUERY

ROOTSTRAP

### PERSONAL INFORMATIONS

Courteous and enthusiastic person, I am interested in IT and everything in its orbit. I recently began to be fascinated by web programming, e.g developing app and building website. Currently focus on learning PHP but exposed in all aspects of web development including front and back end as well. Involved in IT-based project around 2 years for several organizations and wide range company, also have experiences on cloud computing platform such as Google Cloud Platform and having the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### PT. INTERSOLUSI TEKNOLOGI ASIA (BTS.ID) JUNIOR DEVELOPER

12 AUG 2019 - 29 DEC 2020

- Build web applications and features
- Deployment app into server
- Do some research and experiment for new technology

#### SRI BADUGA MUSEUM

**INTERNSHIP** 

10 NOV 2018 - 14 MAR 2019

- Build web applications and eatures
- Deployment apps into server

### STMIK & POLITEKNIK LPKIA CO-ASSISTANT PROFESSOR

2017

Assisting lecturers in teaching and learning activities

#### **EDUCATION**

#### STMIK & POLITEKNIK LPKIA

Associate's Degree of Informatics Engineering

2016 - 2019

Informatics Engineering

#### 14 BANDUNG PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOL

**HIGH SCHOOL** 

2013 - 2016 **Science Major** 

#### **HOBBIES**







